I wasn't wearing makeup that day.
Oh, but it's great, isn't it?
It's like I'm a little stuffed, but I can't say anything.
Lately I've noticed that before a shoot, I get swollen,
I had been thinking about it for a while before the shoot,
But my desire to stretch out prevailed,
The sound of a vacuum cleaner, or the sound of food being cooked,
Limun changes so much.
He started saying, "When Mom comes, I'm going to guess,
When my mom comes over, I get a temporary "guess" version.
The kettle and the idol
Here we are, the hairs and people of Stargast, the kettle.
Today we have another lovely guest, this time an idol.
I'm Serizamoa from Ukka, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
Good day!
Finally, he's here.
Thank you very much for joining us on YouTube.
Thank you very much.
From February to April, we will be on a nationwide tour.
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work. It just ended.
The theme of this tour was to make up a composition with the members, right?
Yes! You made it with the members?
Yes, we did. That was the theme of the tour,
You have been doing more of what the staff has decided for you than I expected, haven't you?
Yes.
But there were some things that we couldn't fully decide on because we were the members,
emissions and so on,
I see.
I see... I was surprised to hear that the staff had worked so much harder on this part.
It was quite difficult because we were doing it by ourselves.
That's amazing.
This time, we were working on the set list, and we were all thinking together about what to say for the first MC.
That's right. Each time we have six members in charge, and each member is in charge of a different part of the show,
If I said, "You should talk about this, too," they would give me advice,
If I said, "You should talk about this too," they would give me advice, but not as a warning.
It's not a warning.
It's not a warning. It's advice.
It's advice.
I see.
Do the customers know who made up the structure for this round?
Um, merchandising.
You don't tell them that?
I don't tell them, but during the sales,
I didn't tell them, but when you buy a certain amount of goods at the sales, you get a postcard,
The postcard is different depending on the voice,
So they knew who it was this time.
That's right.
So we are not trying to sell the staff as an event,
You did it with serious consideration?
We have thought it through.
Wow.
Do you want the group to eventually think about all these things?
We decided on the setlist ourselves,
We thought it up ourselves,
But you are making it from the fans' point of view,
But, I guess it means that you are making it from the fans' point of view.
We think about the excitement of the concert itself,
That's the main point of consideration.
I made it from the point of view of the audience.
That's right.
I make it up as I go along.
How was the sensor meeting?
The sensor meeting was the first time the call ban was lifted.
It was a lucky day, wasn't it?
Yes, it was a bit lucky.
I guess the topic of the MC was also a bit lucky,
I was the MC for a regional event,
I was the MC for a regional tour, and I was able to talk about the calls when the topic was not so good,
I was the MC for a regional tour, and I was able to talk about the calls when the topic was not so interesting. I was like, "Are you having a great time?
It was great to be able to talk about it because it was the first time.
It was great.
Was that the set list that you were originally told by the staff that you were going to release there?
No, it was not.
If you had heard that, would you have thought of something more unique for your own songs?
For example, we made a setlist that would be very exciting for us,
The first song on the list was a new song.
I think it was a song that even the fans wondered if they were allowed to say. I think it was a song that fans were not sure if they were allowed to say,
I thought that we might have made it our standard song.
I see.
Allergies.Allergy
I'll join you in that exercise.
Are you sure?
It's gone because that man is dead.
This program is...
Rei Setouchi.
Shuhei.
Daiki.
Hirofumi-san
This program was sent to you courtesy of Mr. Bad.
Thank you very much.
By Byron